(swans CHIRPING)
(LAUGHING)
You almost lost me back there.
- So, what is this place?
- Someplace special.
I found this on a family camping trip
when I was a kid.
Go on in.
(LAUGHS) Are you serious?
(WATER BUBBLING)
It's warm.
Of course.
They're hot springs, you goof.
Whoo! It's hot!
(MAN SIGHS)
Ooh...
Is this enough?
Well, if you really wanna
go back to nature...
- WOMAN: It's nice and hot.
- MAN: Promise we'll do this every year.
Until we wrinkle.
(MOANING)
MAN: Whoo!
(MAN YELLS)
Nick?
- Sweetie, are you hurt?
- (CACKLING)
NICK: Daria! Ah!
Over here! Ah!
- Nick!
- (NICK GROANING)
- DARIA: Are you OK?
- (PANTING)
- Did you fall?
- No. Someone fucking shot me.
What?
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
- Ahh!
- (LAUGHING)
(WAILING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING, LAUGHING)
MAN: So you had no idea?
He's adopted, you know that.
Thanks, Toni, having only known him
since freshman year.
Still kind of cool, though, right?
Finding out you actually
had some family out there.
We are his family.
That's why we're all here.
And that's why my brother and those guys
are right behind us.
Look, I don't know what to expect.
I don't know these people
or this place.
I could be inheriting a Motel 6.
Or... a meth empire.
I'm just saying,
it's the Appalachians.
Thanks, Vic.
If it'll help,
I did some digging.
- This isn't for one of your columns.
- Of course not.
I'm just the investigative type.
Hobb Springs, established 1926
by families unknown.
Maybe yours.
The first sanitarium in America
outside Battle Creek.
Well, most people would approve.
- Of what?
- Me going into a sanitarium.
(JAZZ PLAYS)
(CHUCKLES)
Agnes Fields.
- You are gonna get yours.
- I'll hold you to that, Mr. Jackson.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(AIR HISSING)
It's more like a health spa, really.
Spas don't come
with their own outhouse, Bryan.
Jillian, it's two weeks, OK?
You know, getting Danny
out in the open air,
seeing how much of an inheritance
this really is.
Really, Rod? Me fixing a tire
is so amazing?
- ROD: Just playing with my new camera.
- Yeah.
And your old camera posted my naked ass
all over the internet last trip!
And got 4,000 hits in one day.
Besides, come on, it's fun.
And fun is just the kind of therapy
we all need.
- Especially my sister and Danny.
- Yeah.
Gotta love therapy.
Wanna start the healing process?
JACKSON: Sally?
You've checked yourself
six times this morning.
- He'll be here real soon.
- I know.
It may take some time.
I can't go another winter.
I need this.
We need this.
We play this right,
sister, he won't
be able to resist you.
Lord knows I can't.
TONI: You guys, it's gigantic.
- VIC: You inherited this?
- DANNY: I guess so.
Our little place in the country.
- VIC: Well, it ain't a Motel 6.
- (TONI LAUGHS)
Couple coats of paint,
and it could be...
Fucking brilliant.
DANNY: Creepy.
TONI: Vic, get out of the car.
I need a moment alone with my boyfriend.
Fine.
It's time to decide.
What do you want to do?
Just when I hit
the lowest I've ever hit,
I got a letter saying
that I belonged to something.
Something that
I gave up on years ago.
Tell me what you wanna do, honey.
I wanna meet these people
and find out what I'm all about.
Oh, my God.
- TONI: Yeah.
- Wow.
- It's huge. (LAUGHS)
- I know, right?
Welcome to Hobb Springs.
- Danny.
- That's right, yeah.
I could tell by your eyes.
I cannot believe that you
are finally here.
- And who are you?
- JACKSON: This would be Sally.
I'm Jackson.
We're the caretakers here.
We weren't expecting your friends,
but, um...
...I'm pretty sure we can
handle you, though.
Oh, we're just the first wave.
This is huge!
MAN: How are we even gonna
find our way around in there?
They call this a spa?
Better leave a trail of breadcrumbs.
We got a flat,
- and then got a little...
- Baked.
Turned around.
I see, no problem.
We have plenty of vacancies coming up.
SALLY: Don't worry, they'll be checking
out today and then we'll have the place
- all to ourselves.
- Oh, goody.
I'd be happy to show you around.
Uh, maybe we could get our bags first.
Yeah, maybe some rooms.
It's been a long drive.
JACKSON: Whatever you wish.
We work for you now.
That's pretty cool, actually.
- Danny has servants now?
- Hey, how you doing?
SALLY: Ya'll come on in.
TONI: Thank you.
Geez.
They're kind of good-looking
for hillbillies.
They're cousins.
No, brother and sister.
Same thing around these parts.
Come on, they're probably just
a normal couple.
- They're funny-looking.
- And Amish.
Actually, we're kissing cousins
on our Quaker brother's sister's side.
I'm so sorry, that was so rude of us.
Ain't nothing we haven't heard before.
Just let it roll off my back nowadays.
So you really are brother and sister?
As I said, we weren't expecting so many.
We can make more, if you'd like.
DANNY: Uh, no, no, it's fine. Really.
We'll leave you hereto rest a spell
while we figure out
how best to deal with you.
What is that?
Go on, sit down.
- (SCOFFS) We're really staying here?
- Why, what's wrong?
Ain't no doubt all of this
is a little bit weird.
- Yeah.
- You guys don't get
the charm of this place?
I do.
You rip the place down,
subdivide the land,
and we go back, we'll send someone in
for a real appraisal.
Yeah, I think you're forgetting
that I don't have anywhere to go.
(SCOFFS) What,
so this is your home now?
I don't know. Maybe.
Danny, you're used
to Central Park West
- and Nobu on Friday nights.
- Yeah. And look what that did to me.
Hey, we don't have to make
a decision right away. It's fine.
This place is alive.
It has history, secrets.
Enough excitement for two weeks
at least.
- Come on, back me up, Vic.
- Uh, sure.
A place this old surely
has a book in it.
- Maybe a movie even.
- Short of murder,
or a Hollywood scandal,
who'd give a shit?
Me, Bryan. We could be talking
about my history.
- So me.
- Yeah, me too.
- Me.
- Gotta stick by family.
(SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYS)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Is that the big, strong man
I rang for?
(PHONE RINGS)
That's more like it.
Hello?
Mr. Jackson?
Hello?! Oh...
(MOANING SOFTLY)
(WHEEZING)
Shhh...
(NECK CRACKS)
- Silly little bitty.
- (LAUGHTER)
A little self control, boys!
That's all I ask!
(LAUGHTER CONTINUES)
(DOOR OPENS)
Oh, my God!
Is that real gold?
Oh, Bryan! These are Hepplewhite!
And tor those that don't watch
Antique Roadshow...
Oh, and they look to be
in perfect condition.
- Oh, they're gonna be worth a fortune.
- A fortune?
How'd you like my place now, Bryan?
Hey, guys.
This place just got a whole lot better.
- TONI: What?
- JILLIAN: Oh, great.
VIC: Where's he going now?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Let's get naked. (LAUGHS)
Whoo!
DANNY: It actually smells sweet.
Hey, guys, if we're gonna do this,
we're gonna do this in style.
- You ready for it?
- BOTH: No! (LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER, LAUGHTER)
- Thanks, man.
- Come on in!
There's room for everybody!
- TONI: Hey. You OK?
- It's really all mine.
(LAUGHS)
I'm still wrapping
my head around that.
Maybe it's just what we needed.
I suppose this will have to do.
Afraid this is all we have right now.
(LAUGHS)
Hello? We're the new owner's
best friends. So you can do better.
(COUGHING)
(SIGHS)
Are we all here?
Now, you boys had your fun
with those bikers.
And you messed
with the little bitty real nice.
Now quit!
Leave Danny alone. Even if it means
giving his friends a pass.
Now I thought I made myself clear!
(GRUNTING)
it won't be long, and you can all
have at 'em as much as you like.
Now you keep doing what you're doing
you're gonna ruin this for all of us!
Do I make myself clear?
Do you understand me?
(GRUNTING)
Fucking family.
So, like, what's the plan
with the cameras, dude?
Like, you're carrying them
around everywhere.
Yeah, man. Look.
Compact and easy to hide.
I think we should put one of these
in Danny's room.
Oh, I'm not up for seeing my sister
naked, but thank you, though.
Well, what about the rest of us, dude?
Fucking asshole!
(FURNITURE SCRAPING ABOVE)
Danny.
Oh, shit.
- (LAUGHS)
- What are you doing?
Please tell me you got a camera for this.
Give it here, give it here.
I'd like to thank the Academy
for this prestigious award.
- I will enjoy this every single day.
- (BOTH LAUGH)
JILLIAN: Tell me how it's fair that we
have to pay for groceries.
Aw...
Poor puppy!
- JILLIAN: Bryan.
- Yeah?
Come check this out.
(INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
You folks just passing through?
BRYAN: No, we're staying
up at Hobb Springs.
You don't say.
I don't get up there much myself
anymore, but I expect I will be.
- Well, why is that?
- You just got in?
- Yeah.
You all see a bunch of little, old
ladies be-bopping around up there?
Oh, yeah.
The Daughters of the Revolution?
That'd be them. Poor things can't
remember if this woman got back
on that bus or not.
Agnes Fields, you hear of her?
No. Like I said,
we just got here, so...
Just what is a lovely couple like you
doing settling in Hobb Springs?
Oh, well, our friend inherited it.
Well, nice for him, huh?
Tell you what.
You take one of these up there,
do me a favor, show it around.
Maybe we get lucky and her face
will ring a bell with somebody.
Oh, is there a reward?
Sure thing, officer.
I can't think what could
have happened to her.
- OK. Well, take care.
- See ya.
What are you doing?
I can't get this hot spot to work.
Have you guys seen Danny?
Yeah, he just wandered
through here a minute ago.
Leave him alone, Mom,
he's enjoying himself.
- Something wrong?
- I don't know.
- Come on. Let's go find him.
- Thank you.
TONI: I guess this place
just gives me the creeps.
TONI: Danny. We've been looking
all over for you.
You OK?
Take a look at this picture
and tell me if I should be.
VIC: That guy kind of looks like Danny.
Even some of the women do.
The whole history
of this hotel's up here.
How could I not know
any of these people?
These pictures only go up to the '70s.
Maybe your side of the family moved.
Not everybody, though. Look.
VIC: I think we just met your cousins.
Whoa, you GUYS-
DANNY: Why the hell
are they all covered up?
I don't know how to break this
to you, man,
but what we have here
is classic mountain breeding.
- DANNY: Stop.
- I'm just saying, there's bound
to be a few defects along the way.
- DANNY: Stop. Seriously.
- You heard him!
You think 'cause we're mountain folk,
our ways ain't fit for fine society?
We've had all sorts stay here,
including three presidents:
Teddy Roosevelt, Calvin Coolidge,
and Jefferson Davis.
Not one had a complaint!
- Jefferson Davis?
- It's OK, Jackson. Really.
He was just messing around.
Weren't you, Vic?
I'm sorry.
I'm just very proud of my heritage.
Families really tamed this land,
they made it into something.
It's impressive. Really.
Yeah.
Wanna see something really impressive?
- Yeah.
- Come on.
Shit!
- Don't touch.
- Sorry.
You have a good eye, Danny.
It belonged to your grandfather.
- He was hell with a bow.
- The bane of critters everywhere.
- What is it, honey?
- My grandfather.
My grandfather.
I just can't believe I...
...even had a grand...
Please. Give it a feel.
Man, that's tight.
Ever been bow hunting, Danny?
Never been hunting, period.
I would like to keep it that way.
That's hardly a proper view, miss,
considering you haven't
even tried it once.
Don't.
- Fit OK?
- I'm getting used to it.
I knew you would.
Your girl, she really
didn't want you to come.
She's just being protective.
They all are.
That guy with the fancy car
and girl to match.
Bryan? We used to work together,
before it all... happened.
I used to be on Wall Street.
Had a bit of a meltdown.
- Seems an appropriate reaction.
- (SCOFFS) Not everybody thought so.
Not my company.
Definitely not my clients.
I lost a lot of people's money.
Including Bryan's, Toni's, my own.
I guess that's when you find out
who your real friends are.
- The ones who stand by you.
- Maybe they think you owe them.
No, not them.
It was all so embarrassing.
You weren't suited to that nonsense.
On the plus side, it's how we found you.
What do you mean?
JACKSON: We do have
the internet out here.
- DANNY: So you found me through Google?
- JACKSON: Yeah.
Took a long time.
But it was important we found you.
- To run a hotel?
- Amongst other things.
Time to climb up.
This doesn't belong to somebody?
Anything on this land
belongs to us.
Go on.
Beer has arrived.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
- There you go, dude.
- Fuck, we need an opener.
- Yeah.
- Hey! Where's Danny?
Out hunting.
- What, Danny?
- What's this?
Oh, yeah. Remember the little gaggle
of old ladies?
- Yeah.
- Well, one of them went AWOL.
Fucking Alzheimer's, dude.
It's a fucking killer.
- You need to go get Danny.
- Now?
Yes. Please.
It's gonna get dark soon, and I don't
like him alone with these people.
OK, Mom.
They ain't gonna like it.
- Are you sure we don't...
- Sh!
...need a permit or anything?
Every man lives by his own set of rules.
Speaking of which,
time to introduce you to the hunt.
First you gotta scout, then stretch.
JACKSON: Someplace the deer feels safe.
Where men can't get to it.
Bait your area.
Lure, entice the deer over your ways.
(DISTANT SCREECHING)
JACKSON: You don't wanna
go after your prey.
You let your prey come to you.
It's about patience.
And being smarter than the animal.
Be still.
Aim for the upper shoulder.
The neck.
Or the brain.
A one-shot kill.
(GRUNTING)
- (EXHALES DEEPLY)
- (LAUGHS)
Now we check the blood trail.
JACKSON: Pink blood with air bubbles
means you've hit the heart or the lung.
Now that's what you want.
Dark red, you probably hit the liver.
The buck may hang in there,
but they will die soon enough.
(GASPING, GRUNTING)
JACKSON: Watery blood with bile,
you may have to track the deer,
deliver another shot.
(GRUNTING)
JACKSON: He may try to bolt.
But if you've aimed just right,
it'll be pure reflex.
(GROANING)
Good shot, Danny.
- What do we do next?
- Nothing.
It's dark red blood.
Besides, he'll be dead soon.
We have more than enough meat back home.
Come on.
We can't just leave it like this.
It's your kill.
Just be careful.
He may have some kick left in him.
Upper shoulder, neck or brain. Go.
JACKSON: Very good, Danny.
That's very good.
(CAR CRASHING)
(GROWLING, GRUNTING)
Charlie, what did you do to this weed?
Oh, fuck this!
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH SHOUTING, GROANING)
Shit!
Jesus!
- You're bleeding.
- So are you.
Most of it's not mine anyway. Ah!
We've gotta get out of here!
He saw my face.
- Who? Are you tripping?
- Not anymore, I'm not.
- This is fucked up!
- Ahh!
- It's him.
- Relax. It's probably just Jackson.
(FOOTSTEPS, GROWLING)
Or not. Here, pull from that end.
Pull from that. Slow, slow, slow!
It's not coming!
It's too twisted!
- Go get some help!
- I can't leave you!
- Go!
- OK.
(SHOUTING)
Ah!
Sorry if it stings, sweetie.
No, no, it's OK.
I'm blaming Vic for that too.
You have to be sure about these woods.
So I heard a buck,
your first time shooting.
It wasn't a buck.
- I killed a doe.
- Even better.
- Is that strong stuff?
- Yeah.
- It sure smells like it.
- It takes some getting used to.
- No, no, it's... it's fine, actually.
I kinda like it.
I do make it myself.
You sit right there.
We'll be right back.
I'm gonna wash this off of my hands.
(GROANING)
Now to get you out
of those bloody things.
All right, it's OK. I can do it.
Now, don't you be that way. I patched up
all my brothers one time or another.
OK. Fine.
All you boys react that way.
I'd say you're strong enough.
You just...
You just have some aches
that need rubbing out.
Toni will be here any second, so...
There's no sense waiting.
You're very important to us.
You don't even know me.
But I know this.
And it beats inside
every one of us.
And with your mind, your schooling,
your strength,
and our blood,
you can have anything you want.
- I still find it hard to believe that.
- Don't you?
TONI: What's, uh... (CLEARS THROAT)
Where have you been?
Jackson brought Danny to me
to tend to.
I got pretty messed up, hon.
Yeah, Vic didn't look so good either.
I should go tend to him.
Think she's gonna help Vic
take off his clothes too?
Oh, come on, stop.
She was just trying to help.
Help herself, obviously.
You look gross. (LAUGHS)
Does it hurt? Oh!
- What is all over your legs?
- Oh, it's ointment.
It's a family formula.
God, you're gonna get infected.
You should lay down.
- Now you're talking.
- Ew! Don't touch me!
- Hey, come on. Come on.
- Don't! Don't touch me.
- You're disgusting. No.
- Please. Come here.
It's not... where's the peroxide?
I had a bad feeling about this.
You going-
Did you actually kill something?
Because it looks like you
rolled around in blood.
Yeah, with a bow and arrow.
- You actually...
- Yeah.
It's pretty cool, huh?
- No!
- Yeah, it is.
No, it's not. I'm not impressed.
- Come here.
- What are you, a hunter now?
Oh, yeah, big time. Big man.
Big man hunter.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
We should pick up hunting.
(PANTING, MOANING)
- CHARLIE: Why so glum, sugarplum?
- Get that thing out of my face.
Can I interest you
in an herbal essence?
Keep that shit away from me too.
You see one mountain monster man,
and you go cold turkey.
- I saw...
- What?
Nothing. Give that to me.
- You. Dude!
- Oh, shoot!
(LAUGHING)
You know what I saw today?
Civil War era.
Flatware. Silver.
What are you doing? (LAUGHS)
Oh, you know.
Just feeling some love tonight.
Now. Go, go, chug!
There we go, there we go.
- There it is! Yeah!
- (LAUGHING)
Give that.
- Hey, man.
- Ah!
- Nice.
- You see any mountain men now? Ahh!
No.
Better.
(KISSING SOUNDS)
- Wait.
- What is it?
(SCREAMING)
- Now I feel better.
- Damn it!
Come on, Jill!
Give us the old Girls Gone Wild.
Fuck you! I'd like to see you guys
do Boys Gone Wild.
What do you mean?
- Now it's a party!
- Get that away!
Sick. You're sick.
- Come on, guys.
- Sorry.
- Yeah!
- Nice!
Just a minute, guys.
ALL: Whoa!
- You OK, man?
- (GASPING)
(TOILET FLUSHES)
Wait a second. You're doing what?
Restoring Hobb Springs.
Top to bottom.
Figure we could have a grand reopening
by next summer.
What did you do to him last night?
- This isn't me.
- It was my decision.
There's something about this place.
Haven't you guys felt different
since you got here?
- Yeah. I've been freaking out.
- Passing out over here.
- Toni?
- No, we're really happy for you, hon.
- But this place...
- Was great. And it can be again.
Do you even know anything about...
about running a hotel, or a spa?
- I'm not just doing it for the money.
- No, we get that. We really do.
Rod? You said that we'd all
make a great web series.
What better way to film a group
of friends restoring a great landmark.
Yeah. I could definitely cut
a good sizzle reel together.
- Make it a rustic Real World.
- DANNY: And Vic?
You said you were game for writing a
book about the history of this place.
- Sure, but...
- See, Bry?
We build awareness.
The rest of it is just
simple business sense
and that's why they
paid us the big bucks.
What do you say, man?
Well, I guess it wouldn't hurt
to draw up a business plan.
I knew you'd come around.
I know what you're gonna say.
Then why are you gonna make me say it?
Did you look at the guy?
It's like night and day.
We were supposed to be going
back to the city.
It's not so easy for me
to just pack it all in, you know.
We came hereto help him.
I don't even know why
we're still friends with the guy!
Oh, my God!
You just don't know when to shut up!
What?
What exactly were you doing with that?
Jillian?
This is Staffordshire.
Do you have any idea
how much these are worth?
How much?
Two thousand, at least.
Cabinet's full of them. I...
I didn't think anyone would notice.
Show me.
Where else have you checked for these?
Just here. I didn't wanna look alone.
All right. I'll bring them to you,
and you catalogue them. OK?
Yes!
H9)'-
Oh, yeah.
These... are perfect.
So secret passages really do exist.
JILLIAN: Yeah, but where do they lead?
Check out those cupboards.
Are we going down there?
They keep priceless antiques
out in the open.
Can you imagine what they
decided to hide?
- JILLIAN: Hey. Are they...?
- BRYAN: Yep.
They're screwing.
What the hell is that?
I think I know.
Get the idea?
Wait.
You're saying that they would just
have sex here
- while people stood by and watched?
- Mm-hm.
Geez. This is one kinky spa.
Whoa, whoa!
- What are you doing?
- Well, I'm agreeing with you.
Kinky, right?
Wait. Are we really gonna do this?
Yeah.
(MOANING, PANTING)
(MOANING, PANTING CONTINUE)
(MOANING LOUDLY)
- (SCREECHING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (CACKLING)
No!
- (CRACKING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (BONES CRACKING)
(SHUDDERING, COUGHING)
(CACKLING)
SALLY: Stop!
You were supposed to wait!
Now you disrespect this room?
Well, go on now!
You might as well
take what you came for.
He stays with me.
- Get!
- (GROWLS)
(BRYAN GROANING SOFTLY)
What those boys did to you...
- You like that?
- (GRUNTS)
Your head's hurt real bad.
But I've seen people live
with a lot worse.
Just let Sally take care of you.
You're so handsome.
I think you like me
rubbing up against you.
BRYAN: No...
No...
I can make you feel better
than that stuck-up bitch you brought.
- (BRYAN GROANS, COUGHS)
- (SALLY MOANING)
JACKSON: Sally!
You're supposed to be saving yourself
for when the time's right.
When's that gonna be?
I know it's hard to wait.
But I'm so close, that I can touch him.
How did this one get in here
to begin with?
I tried to stop 'em.
The fact they stopped at all
is a small miracle.
- They're just not listening.
- Tonight then.
We have them all meet Danny tonight.
You ready?
Finish him off.
Take him to the kitchen.
We'll carve him up later.
SALLY: Don't you fret, lover.
You'll be in me, one way or another.
(GROANING)
(MUFFLED SHOUTING)
(SALLY MOANING)
VIC: Water damage.
Fried outlets.
Mold.
I'm gonna need some more paper.
This would go a hell of a lot faster
if we knew what Danny had in mind.
Where is Danny?
We need keys to some of these places.
Check the front desk.
Only if Wednesday Adams
is on a break.
- Vic.
- Fine.
I'll go, but you go get your boyfriend.
This was all his idea.
TONI: Danny?
Danny?
- Toni! Hey,
- (GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
We could all use a little guidance
out there, please.
OK.
- Did you do all this?
- No.
- TONI: This is Jillian's.
- DANNY: Yeah.
Was she trying to take these?
I don't know.
She and Bry were always going on
about selling things off.
TONI: Without asking you?
When it comes to money,
Bryan's done worse.
- Have you seen them anywhere?
- No.
DANNY: Looks like they took off
with a few parting gifts.
That's not like them, though.
Well, I guess you never
really know anybody, huh?
We've known them for three years.
Yeah, all they've ever been about
is the quick and easy.
Bryan with his subprimes, and Jillian
playing the Manhattan socialite bitch.
- Danny!
- She's from Wisconsin.
I mean, I gave 'em a chance
to get in on the ground floor.
God forbid they ever achieve anything
in life by actually working for it.
- That's what I'm trying to do here.
- Wow, Danny.
- They are your friends.
- You know why Bryan's so eager
to get me back in the firm?
So he didn't have to do any work.
I always did the heavy lifting,
and look what that cost me.
They're my old life.
This... this is my new one.
My God! I am really trying hard
to be supportive right now,
but the only person I don't
feel like I know is you!
- What are you talking about?
- It is this place!
- You wanted to bring me here.
- Because I thought it was gonna help.
And it has!
Even Sally noticed the difference
- from when I got here.
- Oh, my God. Sally?
- Oh, don't start that again.
- You wanna bring up... No, no! No!
Her and her
brother/husband/cousin/whatever.
- Enough of that shit!
- They are the only ones
that we really know nothing about!
How do you not get that?
You wanna know something?
Go ask them yourself.
Yeah, have you?
Have you checked into
anything that
they've told you?
- They have been nothing but kind to me.
- And we haven't?
- You don't understand.
- Oh, my...
- These people are my...
- What?! What are they?!
Do you even know?
You don't even know, Danny!
FUCK you!
Did you get all that?
Look, it's OK. It's OK.
- DANNY: Jackson? Sally?
- JACKSON: In here, Danny.
- I need to talk to you.
- And we with you.
There's so many things we need to
explain, we're just not sure how.
SALLY: I'm sure this is already
so overwhelming for you.
- DANNY: You could say that again.
- And we're thrilled that you're
- interested in the hotel.
- SALLY: But it's already
just such a small aspect
of who we really are.
DANNY: Who are you?
I think it's better if we show you.
But you gotta come alone.
There's members of the family
that have been aching to meet you.
- DANNY: Let's go.
- JACKSON: Come on.
Wouldn't it be easier
to use a flashlight?
It's the way we do things.
You'll see.
(MOANING)
- DANNY: Who are all these people?
- JACKSON: They're all kin,
- one way or another.
- (GIRL LAUGHS)
JACKSON: Come to welcome you home,
Danny.
- (GIRL LAUGHING)
- (GROWLING)
(MOANING, GROWLING)
How long have you been doing this?
We've known each other since our clans
first set foot in these hills.
There were three families
back in those days.
The Craytons, the Boggles
and the Hillickers.
- Which am I?
- You're Hillicker, Danny.
- And all of you?
- We're blood.
Yeah.
JACKSON: Our families tamed this land.
Reaped its rewards,
the coal, the timber.
Others tried to chisel in
on what we'd earned,
but we had birthright.
That's for the lady. That's for you.
- What's that?
- It's the family vintage.
- (MEN LAUGHING)
- (CAR DOORS SLAM)
JACKSON: See, like this brew,
Hobb Springs is a testament to family.
(COUGHING)
JACKSON: It's a place for our folk
to gather from far and wide.
With them came others.
Like your friends came with you.
And they bring temptation to stray.
Weakened our family, muddied our blood.
(GIGGLING)
See, how do you preserve
family strength?
How do you keep it pure?
How?
We stick to our own.
There's nothing to fear, sweetie.
There's nothing to fear.
- What happened to them?
- It's the price of purity.
Purity...
Stick to our own...
That's right, Danny. Family.
Uncle, cousin.
Brother.
See, what was tradition
became ritual.
And that ritual preserved
our blood lines, it cleansed it even.
Our devotion was strong
and rewarded, but when it was weak...
...we were punished.
So it's been for generations.
- Lately, everything has gone wrong.
- No child comes to terms.
The ones that do, they don't survive.
- And that's why we need you, Danny.
- Why?
See, only true blood will keep
this family alive.
What do you mean?
Danny, you and me.
Our blood is still true.
It belongs together.
(SHOUTING)
Get the... Fuck!
Ah! (GRUNTS)
- (LAUGHING)
- Get the fuck off!
Danny!
- Danny!
- I know him.
No. You only think you do.
Danny!
Ah! What the fuck?!
(SCREAMING)
I'm sorry, I...
I don't know who you are.
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(ALL SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING, GROANING)
(GROWLING, GRUNTING)
Flesh is life.
(GAGGING, COUGHING)
Long life.
- (SOFT MUSIC PLAYS)
- (GIGGLING)
(LAUGHING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
- (SALLY MOANING)
- (ALL CACKLING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Danny!
(BANGING)
' Guys.
' Oh!
Jesus, Toni.
Maybe it's Danny or Vic.
Come on.
Here. Toni, stay back.
Ready? On three.
One, two, three!
- Oh, shit!
- Fuck!
I'll say, we almost killed you, man!
Danny! What the hell happened to you?
" Huh?
- What happened?
- I was drinking.
- A lot. (LAUGHS)
- Drinking?
There was dancing.
- Had a barbeque.
- Oh, yeah, sounds nice. Yeah.
Us? We were scared out of a sound sleep
by some maniac banging
on the fucking door!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Calm down.
I don't need this right now, Rod. OK?
Danny... are these scratches?
I don't know. You should know, huh?
♪ Da, da... ♪
- Stop. Stop.
- Hey, come on, dude.
- Danny.
- Come on, get off. Come on.
- DANNY: All right, all right.
- Listen, we need to leave right now.
Fuck that. I'm home.
This is not your home.
You know what? You guys can leave.
Bryan and Jillian, they did.
- Vic did.
- What?
- Vic left?
- Danny, what happened to Vic?
How the fuck should I know?
- V Stop!
- Come on!
- Don't!
You know what, guys? I'm...
Why don't you just let me
get some sleep, please.
Guys, I've never seen him
this fucked up.
- No.
- Should you guys carry him upstairs
- or something?
- Yeah, but what about Vic?
I don't know.
Do you guys smell that?
- Hold on.
- Charlie!
(MEAT SIZZLING)
Oh, fuck. (BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIZZLING)
CHARLIE: Go, go!
(SOBBING)
TONI: We have to get Danny to go.
Whether he wants to or not.
(TONI SOBBING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
Get up, Charlie! Go!
- Toni, go!
- (SOBBING)
(TONI SCREAMS)
- (SHOUTING)
- (SCREAMING)
Get Toni out of here right now!
Go now!
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
(CHARLIE SCREAMING)
(HOOTING, CACKLING)
Ahh!
CHARLIE: Ahh!
(CHARLIE MOANING)
(CACKLING)
(CHARLIE GROANING)
(CHARLIE CHOKING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (CACKLING)
Oh!
(CACKLING)
Where is he, Rod?
We have to find him!
No! We go and come back for help!
- We can't leave him here!
- He wants to stay!
Don't you get that?!
I think he knows what's been going on!
No! No!
You saw when you asked about Vic.
No. Danny would never do that, Rod!
Danny would never do that!
- Listen to your brother for a change!
- No!
Toni! Toni!
Shit!
Toni?
(DISTANT CACKLING)
(LAUGHTER)
- (METAL RATTLING)
- (PANTING)
(METAL CONTINUES RATTLING)
(SCREAMS)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
- (CACKLING)
- (SCREAMING)
(ELECTRICAL HUMMING)
(LAUGHING)
- Please don't shoot me.
- Where's Danny?
- (LAUGHS)
- Where is Danny?!
- Where he belongs.
- What did you do to him?
- Did you do something to him?
- But he liked it.
(MOANING)
He doesn't know what you are.
I do.
L do!
So you think you know all
of our secrets now?
You're murderers!
You eat people!
Don't you judge me.
I'm gonna tell Danny everything
about you.
He knows.
That's why he's staying.
To fill me with a baby.
And I can already feel that baby
coming deep inside.
- On!
- (PANTING)
You're gonna get yours now, girl!
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING, GASPING)
You wanna see what firewater
does to that pretty face?!
- (STEAM HISSING)
- (SALLY GRUNTING)
(SALLY SCREAMS)
Ah!
- (TONI SCREAMS)
- Ah!
DANNY: No!
- What the hell are you doing?!
- (GROANING, PANTING)
DANNY: on, my God, Sally.
It's OK. Sh, sh...
- You're trying to kill my family now?
- Family?
We're your family, Danny.
The ones they killed.
I told you to leave!
Not without you.
You don't know me anymore.
I've changed.
And you don't belong here.
So just go before you get hurt!
Hum?
Like Vic?!
Like Bryan and Jillian, Danny?!
Hurt?! They're not hurt!
They're dead!
Just fucking leave!
- (JACKSON YELLS)
- (SCREAMS)
You fucking hurt my sister. Huh?!
Enough! Enough.
- I said stop!
- Oh, no.
I'm afraid I can't do that, Danny.
She knows an awful lot.
No one will believe her.
She knows that.
- Oh! That is not enough!
- You have me.
I'm a Hillicker now.
You don't need her too.
I'm really sorry.
- You see, we have our ways.
- (SCREAMS)
(CHUCKLES)
Don't worry, baby,
I'm gonna make this real quick.
I'll do it.
- What?
- I said I'll do it.
I brought her here,
and she's my responsibility.
(TONI SCREAMS, SOBS)
- You do it.
- TONI: No!
Make it fucking quick!
(SOBBING) No! No!
On, my God. (SOBBING)
No! No! No! No!
You're taking too long, Danny.
- Run.
- Fucking finish her!
And don't look back.
You fucking...
(TONI GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(TONI SOBBING)
(sum COCKS)
Danny, no.
I told you to leave.
- I tried.
- You didn't listen.
I couldn't.
- Now you've gone and killed one of us.
- He was trying to kill me.
- This isn't happening.
- I can't help you anymore.
(SOBBING) Just stop, Danny!
This isn't you!
No.
It's family.
- (SCREECHES)
- (THUD)
You have a fantastic day, thank you.
DANNY: Hey, guys, how are you?
Find the place OK?
Welcome to Hillicker Springs.
Just you wait until you've experienced
our hot springs.
Boy, are they to die for.
Now, go find your rooms, OK?
Enjoy your stay.
I know I Will.
How are you ladies? Hi.
Hey, how are you?
You enjoying our all-protein buffet?
- I've already lost six pounds.
- Wow!
Don't go disappearing on us now, OK?
(LAUGHS)
Come on, boys, we've got
more important work to do, huh?
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
Come on.
Don't worry.
We'll keep trying and trying.
It's not that.
What then, sweetie?
I'm just happy.
(MID-TEMPO JAZZ PLAYS)
TCS Subtitling